smackapp.com 2016-04-17

# SmackApp | Privacy Policy

## We protect your privacy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for smackapp.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with the smackapp.com website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by smackapp.com to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show smackapp.com ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to smackapp.com website. To opt out of customized Google Display Network ads click here. To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. Any information collected is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site,you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
